>> Jem Young: 互联网工作方式如何 ?
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: How does the Internet work?
因特网在 TCPIP上运行。
Internet runs over TCPIP.
这是每个人都同意的协议
Which is a protocol that
everybody agrees on.
在那包里
And on that packets.
信息包是每个人都知道的信息
The packets are the space you the
information that everybody knows how to
通信。
communicate with.
他们知道如何传输数据。
And they know how to transfer data.
他们知道如何发送数据。
They know how to send data.
有不同的类型
There's different types.
这是 ICMP 包。
There's the ICMP packets.
就是 DIFFTEMP 协议，只是一种检查，如果你愿意的话。
which is the DIFFTEMP protocol,
just kind of a checks, if you will.
这一切都以信托的方式运作。
And it all runs on the series of trusts.
信任意味着如果我把这个包裹发给你
And trust means that if
I send you this packet.
我保证你会把它交给下一个人
I guarantee you're gonna hand
it off to the next person.
我们知道如果我们在浏览器中输入一个域
And we know that if we type
in a domain into the browser,
由使用 DNS 系统的名称服务器解析。
that gets resolved by the name
servers using the DNS system.
这将解析为服务器中某个位置的服务器。
And that resolves into a server
somewhere in the server.
我们会找到那部分的
We'll get to that part.
其他的当然了
For the rest of the course.
但服务器是处理该数据的对象。
But the server is what handles that data.
不错，我们都明白互联网是如何运作的。
Not bad right,
we all understand how the internet works.
现在，如果你想做点政治的话。
Now, if you want a bit of politics.
人们谈论的是网络的中立性以及它的具体内容。
People talk about net neutrality and
what exactly it is.
这是一个信任系统如果我把数据发送给
It's this trust system that if
I send a packet of data to,
我不知道，斯里兰卡我知道我大概会到那里，因为那是
I don't know, Sri Lanka I know that I
will probably get there because that's
就是互联网的运作方式
just the way the internet works.
我们彼此信任
We all trust each other.
我们只保留这些数据
We just keep handing off that data.
网络中立性意味着 ISP 可以这样说，
Net neutrality means
that ISP can say like,
嘿你发短信给斯里兰卡你知道我想做什么
hey, you're sending a text to Sri Lanka,
actually, you know what I wanna do,
我要对进入这个特定区域的所有数据进行征税，因为您
I want to tax every bit of data that comes
into this particular area, because you
知道吗，我可以这么做，而不是这个信任的制度，只是说，
know what, I can do that So rather than
this trust system, Just saying, actually,
我要根据你的数据开始给你充电
I'm gonna start charging you data
depending on where it's going.
如果你再给我一点钱的话
If you pay me a little bit more money.
我保证你的数据会更快
I'll make sure your data gets
there a little bit faster.
这就是网络中立性的辩论。
And that's the debate
between net neutrality.
如果互联网供应商只是这些蠢蛋
Should the internet providers
be just these dumb pipes that
如果我寄一封信就好了吗
if I send a letter it just gets there?
或者，他们应该根据一个人付给我多少钱开始优先处理交通。
Or should they start prioritizing traffic
based on how much someone pays me.
我也没有参加这次辩论我解释了关于
Again, I didn't take a side in this debate
I was explaining what the argument about
中立就是现在你知道了
net neutrality is, now you know.
现在你知道互联网是如何运作的。
And now you know how the Internet works.
所以我说堆满是好的
So where I said the full-stack
is good because
你在后端工作很多都没变
you work on the back-end
a lot it doesn't change.
这是 pythonclock.org 计数器。
This is the pythonclock.org counter.
Python 3 在十年前就出来了
Python 3 came out over ten years ago.
仍然有人使用 Python 2，甚至在 Netflix上
There are still people using Python 2,
in fact even at Netflix,
最近我收到一封邮件，我们即将退休。
I got an email recently,
hey we're retiring Python 2, finally.
那是 11 年前，新版本的 Python 推出。
That was 11 years ago when the new
version of Python came out.
这就是在后端缓慢移动的方式。
That's how slowly things
move on the back end.
所以如果你想要更慢的生活，也许你的包可能是满的。
So if you want the slower life,
maybe full stack might your bag.
把那个扔出去我不会给那些做 Python的人丢人的
Just throwing that out there, I'm not
throwing shade on people that do Python.